tokyoapartments.jp 2011-12-05

# Tokyo Apartments | Privacy Policy

## **PRIVACY POLICY （Protection of Private Information）**

Tokyo Apartments (Enplus Inc) respects the privacy of its users. In this document we explain how   
we use information you supply us via our website. Please note that we reserve the right to change   
the privacy policy in the future. 

## Information Collection and Usage

We collect information about your identity, such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone   
number, etc., for provision of services, billing, and to inform you of new products or services suited   
for your needs. Tokyo Apartments (Enplus Inc) will use customer information to market products   
and services to the customer, but will not disclose or make available any personal information to   
any third parties. 

Tokyo Apartments (Enplus Inc.) will disclose, revise or delete private information provided by a   
customer upon request, after having confirmed the identity of the customer. 

## Security 

Tokyo Apartments (Enplus Inc) restricts access to your personal information to only those employees  
who need it in order to provide our service. We maintain physical, electronic and managerial safeguards   
to protect the confidentiality and security of all personal information transmitted via this website. 

To safeguard your information, our site uses a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which   
encrypts your credit, name and address and other information to be visible only to employees of   
Tokyo Apartments (Enplus Inc).

## Information Disclosure

We will not disclose your personal information to any third parties apart from where you have given  
us your consent to do so. We may provide sales, traffic and demographic statistics and other related   
information to third parties but these statistics will not contain any information which could be used   
to identify any individual customer. 

We reserve the right to access and disclose to third parties your personal information to comply with   
applicable laws and lawful authority requests, to safeguard the proper operation of our systems and   
to protect ourselves and our customers. 

We strive to comply with all applicable laws and regulations, including the Personal Information   
Protection Law of Japan. 

Enplus Inc. January 2009
